A Guide to the Liberty Iron Furnace Collection, 1809-1917
Shenandoah County Library
- Series VII: Ledgers, 1874-1913 (Box 11)
  - Documents found inside page 374-375, Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893 (Folder 11.54)
  - Documents found inside page 382-383, Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893 (Folder 11.55)
  - Documents found inside page 386-387, Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893 (Folder 11.56)
  - Documents found inside page 394-395, Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893 (Folder 11.57)
  - Documents found inside page 396-397, Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893 (Folder 11.58)
  - Documents found inside page 398-399, Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893 (Folder 11.59)
  - Documents found inside page 404-405, Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893 (Folder 11.60)
  - Documents found inside page 406-407, Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893 (Folder 11.61)
  - Documents found inside page 410-411, Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893 (Folder 11.62)
  - Documents found inside page 424-425, Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893 (Folder 11.63)
  - Documents found inside page 438-439, Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893 (Folder 11.64)
  - Documents found inside page 440-441, Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893 (Folder 11.65)
  - Documents found inside page 446-447, Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893 (Folder 11.66)
  - Documents found inside page 448-449, Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893 (Folder 11.67)
  - Documents found inside page 450-451, Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893 (Folder 11.68)
  - Documents found inside page 456-457, Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893 (Folder 11.69)
  - Documents found inside page 460-461, Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893 (Folder 11.70)
  - Documents found inside page 464-465, Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893 (Folder 11.71)
  - Documents found inside page 474-475, Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893 (Folder 11.72)
  - Documents found inside page 494-495, Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893 (Folder 11.73)
  - Documents found inside page 500-501, Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893 (Folder 11.74)
  - Documents found inside page 102-103, Contracts Sale of Bark Book, July 1905 (Folder 11.75)
  - Documents from front cover, Shenandoah Iron and Coal Timebook, July-August, 1905 (Folder 11.76)
  - Document found, "Henry Foltz" page, Day Book, August 1905- January 1913 (Folder 11.77)
  - Documents found inside front cover Liberty Iron Furnace Daily Engineers Report Book Number 2, 1905 (Folder 11.78)
  - Records found inside cover, Bark and Lumber Record Book, 1905 (Folder 11.79)
  - Documents from page 198, Cord Wood and Charcoal Book, 1906 (Folder 11.80)
  - Documents found in page 57 of Shenandoah Iron and Coal Company Day Book, January-August 1909 (Folder 11.81)
  - Bark Records from back cover of Ore Mine and Analysis Record Book, 1909-1910 (Folder 11.82)
  - Documents from page 4-5, Ore Mines and Analysis Record Book, 1909-1910 (Folder 11.83)
  - Documents from page 150-151, Ore and Mines Analysis Record Book, 1909-1910 (Folder 11.84)
  - Documents from page 186-187, Bark Record Book, 1909-1911 (Folder 11.85)
  - Documents from page 190-191, Bark Record Book, 1901-1911 (Folder 11.86)
  - Documents found in Account Book, ca. 1911 (Folder 11.87)
- Series VII: Ledgers, 1874-1913 (Box 13)
  - Shenandoah Iron and Coal, Company Coal Book, 1905-1909
  - Ledger 1889-1890
  - Letter Book "7", January- October 1891
  - Conductor and Engineer Ticket Subs, undated
- Series VII: Ledgers, 1874-1913 (Box 14)
  - Good Delivery Receipts ca 1900
  - Shenandoah Iron and Coal Company, Store Account Book, July 1905
  - Shenandoah Iron and Coal Company Order Book, October 1910
  - Shenandoah Iron and Coal Company Day Book, January -August 1909
  - Wissler, Columbia Furnace, Liberty Furnace Day Book, August 1875-August 1876
  - Shenandoah Iron and Coal Company Day Book, 1906
  - Cash Book, 1890
- Series VII: Ledgers, 1874-1913 (Box 15)
  - Shenandoah Iron and Coal Company, Pig Iron Shipment Book, January -November 1906
  - Shenandoah Iron and Coal Company, Ore Mines and Analyses Record Book, 1909-1910
  - Shenandoah Iron and Coal Company Book, Bark Record Book, 1909-1911
  - Shenandoah Iron and Coal Company Contract, Sales of Bark Book, July 1905
  - Shenandoah Iron and Coal Company Bark and Lumber Record Book, 1908
  - Receivership Ledger, June 1891-February 1892
  - Shenandoah Iron and Coal Company, Wood and Charcoal Record, 1906
- Series VII: Ledgers, 1874-1913 (Box 16)
  - Wissler Liberty/Columbia Furnace Day Book 1874-1875
  - Shenandoah Iron and Coal Company, Time book, July-August 1905
  - Shenandoah Iron and Coal Company, Time book, February-March 1905
  - Liberty Iron Company Journal Number 1, 1892-1894
- Series VII: Ledgers, 1874-1913 (Box 17)
  - Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1892-1893
  - Liberty Iron Company Cash Book, Number 1, 1892-1894
  - Shenandoah Iron and Coal Company Store Accounts Checkbook April 1905
  - Shenandoah Iron and Coal Company Charge Book April 1905
  - Shenandoah Iron and Coal Company Store Checkbook, Undated
  - Shenandoah Iron and Coal Company Charge Book March-April 1905
- Series VII: Ledgers, 1874-1913 (Box 18)
  - Bills Payable, Undated
  - Liberty Iron Company, Charcoal Kilns Book ca. 1890
  - Workmen's Time at Liberty Furnace, Monarch Blast Furnace, 1890
  - Workmen's Time at Liberty Furnace Monarch Blast Furnace, 1890
- Series VII: Ledgers, 1874-1913 (Box 19)
  - Letter Book 1891
  - Shenandoah Iron and Coal Company, Letter Book #4, 1906-1907
  - Cash and Inventory Book 1890-1904
  - S. E. Ledger 1890
  - Receipt Book April-June 1891
  - Letters-Liberty Iron Company, December 14, 1890-January 31, 1891
  - Shenandoah Iron and Coal Company Letter Book, July 1909
  - Liberty Iron Company Checkbook 1892
- Series VII: Ledgers, 1874-1913 (Box 20)
  - Ledger 1890
  - Liberty Iron Company Pay Book February-December 1892
  - Liberty Iron Company Ledger Number 1, 1890
  - Shenandoah Iron and Coal Company Worker Ledger 1905
  - Shenandoah Iron and Coal Company Wood Cutting Ledger February 1905
- Series VII: Ledgers, 1874-1913 (Box 21)
  - Checkbook 1916
  - Account Book 1892
  - Shenandoah Iron and Coal Company "Paid" Account Ledger, 1903
  - Shenandoah Iron and Coal Company Account Book 1909-1911
  - Shenandoah Iron and Coal Company Account Book, ca. 1911
  - Shenandoah Iron and Coal Company Day Book, August 1905-January 1913
- Series VII: Ledgers, 1874-1913 (Box 22)
  - Statement of Engineer, Shenandoah Iron and Coal Company Railroad May-August 1909
  - Statement of Engineer, Shenandoah Iron and Coal Company Railroad July-November 1908
  - Engineer's Report Shenandoah Iron & Coal Company Railroad March-August 1900
  - Statement of Engineer Freight and Passengers Carried, Shenandoah Iron and Coal Company Railroad, September -December 1909
  - Statement of Engineer, Shenandoah Iron and Coal Company Railroad, 1912-1913
- Series VII: Ledgers, 1874-1913 (Box 23)
  - Liberty Iron Company Daily Engineer's Report Book Number 2, 1905
  - Liberty Iron Company Engineer's Daily Reports Number 4, ca. 1890
  - Liberty Iron Company Engineer's Daily Reports, Number 1, undated
  - Liberty Iron Company Engineer's Daily Reports Number 3, undated
  - Shenandoah Iron and Coal Company Delivery Receipt Book, undated
  - Shenandoah Iron and Coal Company Blank Delivery Form Book, undated
  - Shenandoah Iron and Coal Company Checkbook, undated
  - US Brand Bond Book
  - Shenandoah Iron and Coal Company Blank Store Account Checkbook, Undated
  - Shenandoah Iron and Coal Company Wood Contract Checkbook, undated
- Series VII: Ledgers, 1874-1913 (Box 24)
  - Shenandoah Iron and Coal Company Design Drawing Notebook, undated
  - Disposition of Letters, ______, and Enclosures sent Various Pictures, January 1891
  - Shenandoah Iron and Coal Company Order Book, January 1911
  - M.M. Campbell Receivership Account Book, ca. June 1891
- Series VII: Ledgers, 1874-1913 (Box 25)
  - Time Book ca. 1911
  - Time Book, January 1891-March 1892
  - Cash Book 1890-1891
  - Lumber Book, 1891
- Series VII: Ledgers, 1874-1913 (Box 27)
  - Day Book, January-April 1883
  - Day Book, 1890-1891
  - Liberty Iron Company, Liberty Furnace Reports #9, May 1892-January 1893
  - Liberty Iron Company Monthly Sales Book Number 1, May-June 1891
  - Cash Book, 1891
- Series VII: Ledgers, 1874-1913 (Box 28)
  - Ledger May 1890-January 1891
  - Shenandoah Iron and Coal Company Worker Journal, 1905
  - Account Book, January-March 1891
  - Wissler Columbia/Liberty Iron Furnace Day Book, September 1876- December 1878
  - Liberty Iron Furnace Day Book, 1879-1880
  - Notebook, Undated
  - Time Book, October 1891-March 1892
- Series VII: Ledgers, 1874-1913 (Box 29)
  - Ledger, Liberty Iron Company 1891
- Series VII: Ledgers, 1874-1913, Statement Showing the Assessed Value of Railroad, Electric Railway and Canal Property in the Commonwealth of Virginia, 1910 (Oversize OVERSIZE FOLDER 1)
- Series VII: Ledgers, 1874-1913, Statement Showing the Assessed Value of Railroad, Electric Railway and Canal Property in the Commonwealth of Virginia, 1911 (Oversize OVERSIZE FOLDER 2)
- Series VIII: Maps and Plats, Land Including Old Newman Bank, 1899 (Oversize OVERSIZE FOLDER 4)
- Series VIII: Maps and Plats, Marr and Dean Land, March 1891 (Oversize OVERSIZE FOLDER 5)
- Series VIII: Maps and Plats, Unidentified Survey Drawing, undated (Oversize OVERSIZE FOLDER 8)
- Series VIII: Maps and Plats, Railroad Plat Drawings, undated (Oversize OVERSIZE FOLDER 7)
- Series VIII: Maps and Plats, Deerhead Tract of 105 Acres, February 1891 (Oversize OVERSIZE FOLDER 7)
- Series VIII: Maps and Plats, Columbia and Liberty Lands Maps, undated (Oversize OVERSIZE FOLDER 9)
- Series VIII: Maps and Plats, Consolidated Plats Liberty and Columbia Iron Furnace Tracts Undated (Oversize OVERSIZE FOLDER 11)
- Series VIII: Maps and Plats, Liberty Tract Plot Maps, Undated (Box OVERSIZE BOX 1)
- Series VIII: Maps and Plats, Consolidated Plot Columbia and Liberty Tracts (Box OVERSIZE BOX 1)
- Series VIII: Maps and Plats, Rail Line Plat Map Surveys, Undated (Box ROLLED STORAGE BOX 4)
- Series VIII: Maps and Plats, Liberty Furnace Tract Survey, Undated (Box ROLLED STORAGE BOX 4)
- Series VIII: Maps and Plats, Rail Line Plat Survey Map, Undated (Box ROLLED STORAGE BOX 6)
- Series VIII: Maps and Plats, Plat Survey Maps, Rail Line to Ore Washers Liberty Iron Furnace, Undated (Box ROLLED STORAGE BOX 6)
- Series VIII: Maps and Plats, Rail Elevation Maps, Undated (Box ROLLED STORAGE BOX 6)
- Series VIII: Maps and Plats, Railroad Plat Survey Map, Undated (Box ROLLED STORAGE BOX 7)
- Series VIII: Maps and Plats, Rail Line Plat Maps, Undated (Box ROLLED STORAGE BOX 8)
- Series VIII: Maps and Plats, Consolidated Tract Columbia and Liberty Furnace Plots Survey, Undated (Box ROLLED STORAGE BOX 8)
- Series VIII: Maps and Plats, Rail line Plat Map, Undated (Box ROLLED STORAGE BOX 8)
- Series VIII: Maps and Plats, Rail Line Plat Survey Maps, Undated (Box ROLLED STORAGE BOX 8)
- Series IX: Technical Drawings, Railroad and Machinery Technical Drawings, undated (Oversize OVERSIZE FOLDER 10)
- Series X: Payroll Records, Payroll Sheets 1905-1906, 1 of 4 (Oversize OVERSIZE FOLDER 12)
- Series X: Payroll Records, Payroll Sheets 1905-1906, 2 of 4 (Oversize OVERSIZE FOLDER 13)
- Series X: Payroll Records, Payroll Sheets 1905-1906, 3 of 4 (Oversize OVERSIZE FOLDER 14)
- Series X: Payroll Records, Payroll Sheets 1905-1906, 4 of 4 (Oversize OVERSIZE FOLDER 15)
- Series X: Payroll Records, Receipts, July/August 1907 (Oversize OVERSIZE FOLDER 16)
- Series X: Payroll Records, Payroll Sheets 1908 (Oversize OVERSIZE FOLDER 17)
- Series X: Payroll Records, Payroll Sheets 1909 (Oversize OVERSIZE FOLDER 18)
- Series X: Payroll Records, Payroll Sheets 1910 (Oversize OVERSIZE FOLDER 19)